Experience their lives on the road
One Direction: This Is Us is a documentary, music
film directed by Morgan Spurlock.
"One Direction: This Is Us" is a captivating and intimate all-access
look at life on the road for the global music phenomenon.
Weaved with stunning live concert footage, this inspiring feature film tells the remarkable story of Niall, Zayn, Liam, Harry and Louis' meteoric rise to
fame, from their humble hometown beginnings and competing on the X-Factor, to conquering the world and performing at London’s famed O2 Arena.
Hear it from the boys themselves and see through their own
eyes what it's really like to be One Direction.
Self, played by Harry Styles.
Self, played by Zayn Malik.
Self, played by Liam Payne.
Self, played by Niall Horan.
Self, played by Louis Tomlinson.
Self, played by Simon Cowell.
One Direction: This Is Us is a 2013 documentary concert film about four
parts English and one part-Irish boy band One Direction.
It opened in the United Kingdom on 29 August 2013.
It also opened a day later in the United States.
The film follows the group on their Take Me Home Tour.
It was a commercial success and grossed $68 million worldwide.
The tone is uplifting.